Jonathon Van Ausdal

jonathonvanausdal257@gmail.com 385.484.1260

Summary

Software Engineer with experience in a MERN environment. Highly motivated. I work well on a team or solo. demonstrated working knowledge of Bootstrap, CSS, Express.js, Git, Github, Heroku, HTML (HTML5), JavaScript, JQuery, MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js, React, SEO, Responsive Design, API/JSON, RESTful API, State Management, Command Line, Database Theory, Agile Methodologies, Quality Assurance Testing, Social Coding Best Practices, Computer Science Fundamentals

Core Technologies

• React

- CSS
- JavaScript
 - HTML
- Agile Scrum
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Apollo/Graphql
- MongoDb/MySQL

Experience

University of Utah Coding Bootcamp Program

University of Utah

January 2022 - Present

Salt Lake City, Utah

- Created a portfolio for class assignments and projects.
- Worked solo and on a team.
- Experience with using Github, Heroku and Github Pages.
- Introduced to MySQL and MongoDB.
- Ensure teams follow design patterns and frameworks using shared APIs

Pane-less Window Washing

Web Site Development

May 2022 – September 2022

American Fork, Utah

- Create and Maintain a website for Pane-less Window washing.
- Implemented using MERN stack. (MongoDB, Express, React, Node).

Down Town Furniture

Furniture Delivery

August 2020 – January 2021

Saint George, Utah

- Operated a propane forklift and Baltimore lift.
- Responsible for delivering furniture in a quickly and timely manner.
- Operated box truck safely.
- Responsible for stocking the store floor with furniture to be sold.
- Used hand tools to assemble furniture.
- Always used safety precautions to lift and transport heavy furniture.

Education

- American Fork High School 2017
- One year of study at UVU towards Computer Science.
- University of Utah Web Coding Bootcamp Program November 2022
- Self-directed learner



References

- Taylor Down Town Furniture (435) 628-5812)
- Jonah Down Town Furniture(385)292-2487)
- Max —- Clearlink(801)855-5136)